you know good morning something about something interesting about this internet interesting
fascinating annoying etc is that what it's doing algorithmically is it is constantly bringing
a bunch of people into a room at different points in their timeline and so what happens
is that you will constantly be interacting with people at like their first time and because of
its individual nature they think that you should be meeting them at their first time energy every
time so like i've got people that are just now seeing that i did this interview with tasha k
who are like seeing this for the first time they have their feelings about it they have their uh
their ire about it etc etc i did that interview in december of last year and
my annoyance my frustration my damn i shouldn't have done that interview happened in december of
last year people are just seeing it now and want me to be meeting them at their first phase of confusion
confusion or annoyance or disgust etc and so because i'm not they are like i don't know well
every week they're kind of trying to come with some new reason to discredit me so this week the reason
to discredit me is you did an interview with tasha k you should have known better how dare you so that
that that's this week's discredit discreditation okay the thing about it though is that i have already
addressed this and i am not no one is able to keep meeting people you know what let's not even say able
no one should be expected to keep meeting people at their individual places in their timeline
it's not possible it's not practical you're in your timeline this internet is inserting folks
into your timeline on their timeline and the ego is what forces people to think that you owe them
you owe them i like you you you owe them some sort of um identifying of where they're where they're
stepping in it's the same reason why when i'm on live and people come in and they announce i'm here what
are we talking about it what are we talking about and i'm always saying like just join the flow
just join the flow you know the other thing is i need y'all to really grasp that i will use things
like tasha k or i will use big headline items to talk about the root items that we don't get to talk
about that is that is a necessity because this algorithm only feeds off the toxicity so you splash
the toxicity out there and then you spring it down with the truth and you know like someone here is
saying i think people expected more from a person has educated you to kind of do some research blah blah blah
blah blah blah the the the constant effort to try to hold me to some false sense of
uh perfection as a counter to me holding people to a very generic bottom line sense of morality
is not gonna fly it's not it's not it's not it's not gonna fly it's not gonna fly like i there's a
very difference between making errors and making choices there's a very big difference between making
errors and making choices right you know people who are making a choice even though they know the
fuckery that's very different very different you know people are like how do you not know about tasha
k baby that woman is not in she's not in my orbit she's not in my orbit in the same way that people
think amanda seals isn't doing anything when i just dropped a whole album and i'm doing interviews
with folks all over the world but those folks are not in their orbit right and so that's what social
media does it gives you this like false sense that whatever you're seeing is what everyone's seeing and
it's not you know it's not um this woman the mushroom he was supportive and then i saw him under a post
saying that he didn't like my brand of autism because he says he feels that i speak about autism
from a autism supremacist point of view so he was blocked that's how that happened so um i just want to
start you all today with it there you go born to shine forever get them together get them together
um no i had already done the interview when i did that live so what are you talking about
kelechi can you check your fucking whatsapp kelechi don't be checking her whatsapp y'all good morning
kelechi i know y'all want to see another kelechi amanda interview because she is brilliant and i am
brilliant together we are brilliant together
um so yeah you're not gonna get me here's the thing you're not gonna get me to feel bad about
myself and that's that's the thing you know we don't do enough teaching and love so we are
constantly doing the practice of teaching and shame because so many folks just simply won't
learn without shame okay they just won't learn without shame we we see that all the time like
these crackers they don't learn without shame they they don't um and you know even if i do go on
let's say let's just say for for what it's worth let's just say i did know the full extent of this
tasha k person um i didn't go on her platform and and big her up like i didn't go on her platform and
support her ideologies etc etc like folks someone in here said folks go on opposers platforms to have
discussions all the time yes however i i am expected to do what everyone thinks i'm supposed to do
even though none of these people have nothing to do with me so you're never gonna get me to feel
bad about myself shame is not an effective tool for me and the other part of it is that um
i am not going to feel bad about myself about about errors that i have made in genuine error
like i'm just not i'm not i'm not doing that no more you know so many of us are plagued our whole
lives with that you know with like you can't make a fucking mistake you know then you become a
perfectionist then you you develop ocd i mean it just goes really far and by the way you're getting
you're getting this from people who don't hold themselves to the same standard that's the other
part you're getting that from people who don't hold themselves to the same standard pass their shit back
to them y'all pass it back pass it back create the standard upon which you want to live
okay and oh kalechni the likability the likability conversation is so disingenuous because none of
them people are likable like if you're having a conversation about likability you're not likable
that there's that and um i am liked by the people i like i like kelechi kelechi like me
do you see how that work that's that's it that's it i like my man he like me i like my friends they
like me i like gary at the post office he like me you see what i'm talking about you see what i'm
talking about you see what i'm talking about you don't even you don't need everyone to like you
it's not even realistic and it's impractical and honestly it's very stressful i would imagine
i don't get invited to be in people's weddings and i love that for me i love that for me
i love that i've never been a bridesmaid i love that for me you know who else like me
come here bubba come here bubba he liked me so much he want me to pet him look look look look
yeah yeah and when people want you to care that they don't like you it's like i can't
i can't i've been really really working on i only keep people in my life who can correct me in love
that's it i only correct me i only keep people in my life that correct me can correct me in love
if you have to correct me and like the other day i did not practice that and i got checked
and i had to check myself i had to check myself you feel me because it's not something we're taught
enough right it's not a practice you know adrian marie brown has a book called loving corrections
and it's not always effective right because you have so thank you miller because you have so many
people who are really deep deep deep right and um they're really deep deep deep in the mire
so at the end of the day it's it's not always effective but for for many of us so i'll tell you
a little story like when i was in gymnastics my coach used to yell crazy at us right he used to yell
crazy at us you know how gymnastics is so he used to be yelling like god damn it do it right blah blah
blah blah blah blah blah okay and um and i had to tell him as a 14 year old hey bro i don't work well
with that you can keep that same volume instead however can you use positive reinforcement because
that would really work for me and he went from all that rah rah to come on tiger
effective effective you know like me and my engineer the wonderful beautiful amazing matt cody
who um did my project truth translator we were having a communication issue you know and and it was and
it was like one of those things where i'm like no like we we are very aligned so if we're having a
communication issue like i need to get to the bottom of that right and so i one night i was like okay like
i just need to ask you some questions so i can understand your communication style and let me just
say this too questions really flood like they fluster people but for someone like me questions are not being
done to like undermine they're being they're being asked to undergird do you understand the difference
some people are asking questions disingenuously they're trying to um sort out some bullshit etc etc
i am asking questions to create a foundation upon which we can build i'm asking questions so that we can
get to like a a shared um uh so we can get to like a an agreement space right so we can get to common ground
that's what i'm that's why i'm asking questions and so because we live in such a disingenuous society
that is built on narcissism the concept of asking questions can be very very offensive to people
right but for someone who's like neurodivergent like me like questions are like the the the very
um fabric of my existence okay i'm asking myself questions all day long should you have said that that
way what do you think about that what's a better way to do that how what is that why do you do that
that way right i love when people ask me questions and it's so interesting to see how when um when people
are not used to being able to ask questions they also don't even know how to ask you questions
right because they're so used to being to questions being seen as a um a negative so like even even with
my partner like like encouraging him to like ask me questions i don't get offended by that i like it
i like it it helps me understand me it helps you understand me right so um with the questions thing
it's it's yeah my metacognition is off the charts i've been metacognitioning all day long so with the
questions thing it's like i'm always trying to understand and so me and matt i literally was so
happy that he just let me ask him some questions about how he receives information so that i could show
up better in communication right so like some of the questions i asked him were like okay are you
when i say a thank you mf braylon when i say a sentence when i when i give you a um a response of
notes right um i will neon rosebud when i give you a response about notes do you find yourself
um responding more to the detail or do you find yourself responding more to the overarching message
do you find yourself being attracted to the negative at like on the scale of one to ten how
attracted are you to the negative versus the positive like these are the types of questions
i was asking him to help me learn how to communicate to him better and when i'm telling you
after we didn't have the same problems i will do that kufia awesome we didn't have the same problems
after that because i was able to take that assessment and apply it differently so it allowed me to um
change how i was communicating with him so now it was like instead of just giving him the overall
when i'm giving him my notes i know that i need to be very very very detailed and i need to do it
um like separately right it let me know that like i need to start with a very genuine not genuine that's
not where i'm looking for it is genuine but i need to start with a very general positive right um i need
to and i need to not list i need to confer about each item separately because if i give him all of them
all at once they all flood together and then it creates confusion and so this was like super duper
useful and it was only able to happen because he was generous enough to engage in the back and forth
without feeling like he was being probed you know and he was like and after he was like you know thank
you like i've never had anyone like take the time to like try to understand my communication style
um and i'll be honest it was the first time that i had ever done it in such a deliberate way i think
we i think we do that over time kind of naturally sometimes but this was like i'm gonna make a deliberate
point to do this and it just made the difference really so um i say all of that to say that you know i'm in a
constant practice of trying to be um my most effective human self in this experience
and i consider effectiveness and i consider effectiveness attached to growth no not my man
my producer i consider effectiveness not my producer sorry my engineer attached to growth how
how how much opportunity for growth and life am i creating space for and that is what i consider the
measure of my efficacy as a human that's what's up kiki so i hope you all have a good day i hope this
gave you all some insights and um and uh smell the flowers